{
    "subject": "resource/Point_Arguello_Launch_Complex_B",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedRocket",
    "object": "resource/Nike-Cajun",
    "human_readable": "Point Arguello Launch Complex B is associated with Nike-Cajun.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9460620284080505,
            "question": "What is Point Arguello Launch Complex B associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.920503556728363,
            "question": "Name a project linked to Point Arguello Launch Complex B."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.920377254486084,
            "question": "Which launch complex is connected to Nike-Cajun?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.890254020690918,
            "question": "Are there any other launch complexes associated with Nike-Cajun?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8085460066795349,
            "question": "Is Nike-Cajun related to a specific launch site?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7848252058029175,
            "question": "What type of facility is Point Arguello Launch Complex B?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7589084506034851,
            "question": "Can you provide an example of a program using Point Arguello Launch Complex B?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6862714886665344,
            "question": "How is Point Arguello Launch Complex B used today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6852990388870239,
            "question": "What historical significance does Point Arguello Launch Complex B hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.577542245388031,
            "question": "What geographical location is Point Arguello Launch Complex B situated in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Point Arguello Launch Complex B is associated with Nike-Cajun.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5839_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical significance does Point Arguello Launch Complex B hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5839_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Point Arguello Launch Complex B used today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5839_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide an example of a program using Point Arguello Launch Complex B?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5839_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5839_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5839_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5839_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5839_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5839_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5839_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5839_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5839_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5839_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5839_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the format you requested:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because according to the provided documents, Launch Complex B or LC-B at the Point Arguello Naval Air Station in California, United States was a launch complex which was used for twenty three sounding rocket launches between 1960 and 1963, and Nike-Cajun rockets were launched from the complex whilst it was active."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the statement that Point Arguello Launch Complex B is associated with Nike-Cajun, as this rocket is mentioned multiple times in relation to the launch complex."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}